Guide to the Records of American Association for Ethiopian Jews (AAEJ), undated, 1960-1961, 1963, 1965-1968, 1970-1995, 2001-2002 *I-503
American Jewish Historical Society, Boston, MA and New York, NY
- Subgroup II: AAEJ Activists, undated, 1961, 1963, 1966, 1968, 1970-1993; Boxes 38-139.
  - Series A: LaDena Schnapper (AAEJ Coordinator) Files, undated, 1961, 1963, 1966, 1968, 1970-1991; Boxes 38-120.
    - Subseries 3: Schnapper's Chicago AAEJ General Files A-Z, undated, 1961, 1966, 1971, 1973, 1975, 1977-1990; Boxes 90-120.
      - Beliak, Rabbi Ben, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 13)
      - Ben-Gurion, David - Centennial Committee, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 14)
      - Berg, Alan, 1983-1984 (Box 90, Folder 15)
      - Berger, Dr. Graenum - Book/Biography, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 16)
      - Berger, Graenum - Biography, undated, 1963?, 1985, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 17)
      - Berger, G. - Correspondence (see OS1F Folder 1), undated, 1979, 1983-1988 (Box 90, Folder 18)
      - Berger, G. - Medal of Freedom, 1981, 1983-1987 (Box 90, Folder 19)
      - Berger, Graenum and Emma Scholarship Fund - November 1985, 1985-1986 (Box 90, Folder 20)
      - Berger Mail, 1982-1983 (Box 91, Folder 1-2)
      - Berger Mail (see OS1F Folder 1), undated, 1984-1986 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Bergman, Rabbi Robert, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Berkeley Theater, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Berkman, Marc, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Berman, Collette, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Better Business Bureau, undated, 1982-1983 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Bibliography, undated, 1981, 1984, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - Bibliography: Who's Who in African Affairs in Washington, D.C., 1981 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Black Jews (see OS1F Folder 1), 1980, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - Black Media Project - AJC, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - Blacks, undated, 1982-1983 (Box 91, Folder 13)
      - Blacks - Orig., Offers, etc., 1984 (Box 91, Folder 14)
      - Blackwell, Qaturah, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 15)
      - Blazer, Phil (see OS1F Folder 1), 1985 (Box 91, Folder 16)
      - B'nai B'rith Canada Trip - March 1984 (Box 91, Folder 17)
      - B'nai B'rith Conference, Las Vegas - August 24-28, 1986, undated, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 18)
      - B'nai B'rith Material, 1982-1983, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 19)
      - B'nai (Shlomo Kuperstein), 1989 (Box 91, Folder 20)
      - B'nai Torah Stationery, undated (Box 91, Folder 21)
      - B'nai Torah, 1982-1984 (Box 91, Folder 22)
      - Board of Jewish Education - New York, 1985-1986 (Box 91, Folder 23)
      - Board Mailings, 1982-1985 (Box 91, Folder 24)
      - Board Mailing (started February 1987), 1986-1987 (Box 91, Folder 25)
      - Book Bank USA, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 26)
      - Book - The Last of Days, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 27)
      - Books - Red Sea Press, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 28)
      - Books (see OS1F Folder 1), undated, 1981-1983, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 29)
      - Bornstein, Ben, undated, 1983, 1985-1988 (Box 91, Folder 30)
      - Boshewitz, Rudy, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 91, Folder 31)
      - Boston Folder, undated, 1981-1985 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Bracelets (see OS1F Folder 1), undated, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Brichto, Herbert - Chanan Writings, 1968, 1973, 1975-1976, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Brochures, undated, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Bronstein, Deborah, 1985-1987 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Bronstein, Steve, undated, 1985, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Bronstein, Steve, undated, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Brooks Letter, undated, 1982-1983 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Brown, Philip P., 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Bulletin Board, undated (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Bulletin Board Material, undated (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Burdick, Senator, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Burdick, Quentin, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 13)
      - Burg, Yosef, undated (Box 92, Folder 14)
      - Business Cards, undated (Box 92, Folder 15)
      - Buttons, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 16)
      - CARE, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 92, Folder 17)
      - CBF - World Jewish Relief, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 18)
      - Cabbage and Kings - February 2, 1985, 1985-1986 (Box 92, Folder 19)
      - Canadian Jewish Congress, undated, 1983, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 20)
      - Calendar 1987 (see OS1F Folder 1), 1986-1987 (Box 92, Folder 21)
      - Call to Conscience - September 17, 1986, 1980, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 22)
      - Camps (see OS1F Folder 2), undated, 1983-1984 (Box 92, Folder 23)
      - Canada, undated, 1982-1984 (Box 92, Folder 24)
      - Canada - Ethiopian Jews of Canada Organization, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 25)
      - Canada - JIAS, Montreal EJ Community Meeting - April 14, 1986, undated, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 26)
      - Canadian Association for Ethiopian Jews, undated, 1981-1989 (Box 92, Folder 27)
      - Canadian Physicians for African Refugees, 1980, 1983-1984 (Box 92, Folder 28)
        1.) Typewritten letter from Mark Doidge to Nate Shapiro, July 10, 1980
        2.) Typewritten letter from Mark Doidge to Nate Shapiro, September 6, 1984
      - Canadian Physicians for African Refugees, undated, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Canadian Physicians for African Refugees - Letters to LaDena in Ethiopia, undated, 1990-1991 (Box 93, Folder 2-3)
      - Capitol Hill Update, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Cards - Calendars, undated, 1982-1984, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Cards - Hanukah - In Honor of, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Cartoons, undated, 1984-1985 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Catalogs, 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Census (Names Gathered in Israel - AAEJ Names), undated, 1982, 1986-1987 (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - CCAR Conference - June 16, 1984, New York, undated, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Central Conference of American Rabbis, June 1985, Minneapolis, 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Center for Jewish Activism, undated (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Chai Campaign Info, undated (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Chai Program, undated, 1982, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Chai Sponsorship, undated, 1985-1988 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Chai Sponsorship - Completed and no responses, 1983-1985 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Chamah (see OS1F Folder 2), undated, 1984-1986 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Change of Address (ML), 1986-1987 (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Chase, Jaffa, undated, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Chicago Action for Soviet Jewry, undated, 1989 (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Chicago AAEJ Group, undated, 1983-1985 (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - CARPCV (Chicago Area Returned Peace Corps Volunteers), 1984-1985, 1987-1990 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Chicago Area Temples, undated (Box 94, Folder 14)
      - Chicago Board of Rabbis Mailings, undated, 1983-1984 (Box 94, Folder 15)
      - Chicago City Resolution, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 16)
      - Chicago - Department of Human Relations, 1983, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 17)
      - Chicago Jewish Federation (see OS1F Folder 2), 1983-1986 (Box 94, Folder 18)
      - Chicago Jewish Folk Arts Festival - Summer 1986, undated, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 19)
      - Chicago Pledges Dinner 1981 (Box 94, Folder 20)
      - CSAE (Chicago Society of Association Executives) (see OS1F Folder 2), undated, 1983-1984 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Chicago Volunteer Chapter, undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Children's Kits, undated, 1984-1985 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Chinn, Janice, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Christian Broadcasting Network, undated, 1975, 1977-1978, 1980, 1984-1985 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - City Club, undated (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Clothing, undated, 1979-1985 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Clothing, ELAL, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Clothing - Ethiopian Designs, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Clothing Shipments, 1985-1986 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Cohen, Jonathan, undated (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Cohen, Sara, 1985-1988 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Cohen, Scott, 1985-1988 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - Cohn, William, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - Cohn, Willie - An Immigrant from Ethiopia Am I paper, Summer 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - Coins, Medals, undated, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - College of St. Scholastica, undated, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 17)
      - CAER - Committee to Aid Ethiopian Refugees - N.Y., undated, circa 1987 (Box 95, Folder 18)
      - Computers, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 19)
      - Computer / Amharic (Dashen Engineering), undated, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 20)
      - CAJE Conference - Alternatives in Jewish Education, undated, 1982-1983, 1985, 1987, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 21-22)
      - Conference Call / Activists, undated (Box 95, Folder 23)
      - Conference on Alternatives for Jewish Education - August 27-31, 1984, Palo Alto, CA, undated, 1984-1985 (Box 95, Folder 24)
      - CAJE Conference - August 1984, undated, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 25)
      - CAJE Conference - Northern, IL, August 11-15, 1985 (see OS6F Folder 1), undated, 1984-1986 (Box 95, Folder 26)
      - CAJE - Crisis in Ethiopia, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 27)
      - Conference - United Synagogue of America - N.Y., November 14-17, 1985 - Fellman, Jane (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Conferences, 1983, 1985-1986 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Conferences, 1985-1987 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Confidential, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Congress of the United States, 1985-1986 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Congressional Action, undated, 1983-1986, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Congressional Action - Famine, undated, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Congressional Addresses, undated, 1981, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Congressional Advocacy Package, undated (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Congressional Caucus, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Congressional Delegation - Ethiopian Trip - November 1984 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Congressional Human Rights, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - Congressional Letters, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - Congressional Letters - 1986, undated, 1982-1983, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - Congressional Material - AAEJ Activities, 1983-1984 (Box 96, Folder 15)
      - Congressional Material - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 16)
      - Congressional Materials / Articles, 1983-1985 (Box 96, Folder 17)
      - Congressional Meetings - July 18-19, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 18)
      - Congressional Record - June 28, 1984 Solidarity Week, 1983-1984 (Box 96, Folder 19)
      - Congressional Record Articles, June 1984 (Box 96, Folder 20)
      - Congressional Resolution, May 1988 (Box 96, Folder 21)
      - Congressional Senate Resolution 55, 1983, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 22)
      - Congressional - U.S. Senate Letter for Sudan Rescue, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 23)
      - Cong. Tom Lantos, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 24)
      - Congress People, undated, 1982-1984, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 25)
      - Contribution Form, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 26)
      - Contributions to AAEJ $1000 and over, 1982-1984 (Box 96, Folder 27)
      - Coro, R., undated, 1981-1982, 1986-1987 (Box 96, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence 1984 A (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence 1984 B (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence 1984 C (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence 1984 D (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence 1984 E (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence 1984 F (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence 1984 G (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence 1984 H (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence 1984 I (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence 1984 J (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence 1984 K (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence 1984 L (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence 1984 M (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence 1984 N (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence 1984 O (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence 1984 P (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence 1984 R (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence 1984 S (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence 1984 T (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence 1984 U (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence 1984 V (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence 1984 W (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence 1984 Y (Box 98, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence (Misc.) to Graenum Berger, Henry Rosenberg, Lenhoff, etc., 1983-1984 (Box 98, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence 1985-87 A, 1985-1987 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence 1983-88 B, 1983-1988 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence 1984-87 C, 1984-1987 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence 1985-87 D, 1985-1987 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence 1984-85, 1987 E, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence 1984-87, 1990 F, 1984-1987, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence 1984-88 G, 1984-1988 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence 1984-87 H, 1984-1987 (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence 1985-86 I, 1985-1986 (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence 1984-87 J, 1984-1987 (Box 99, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence 1984-88 K, 1984-1988 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence 1985-87 L, 1985-1987 (Box 99, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence 1985-88 M, 1985-1988 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence 1985-87 N, 1985-1987 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence 1985 O (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence 1985-86 P, 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence 1985-87 R (contains photographs), 1985-1987 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence 1984-87 S, 1984-1987 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence 1985-87 T, 1985-1987 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence 1985-86 V, 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence 1985-89 W, 1985-1989 (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence 1984-86 Y, Z, 1984-1986 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence from Important People, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence Misc., undated, 1983-1984 (Box 100, Folder 12)
      - Council of Jewish Federations Meeting January 5, 1987, New York, undated, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 13)
      - Council of Jewish Federations - New York, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 14)
      - Court, Allan, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 15)
      - Cranston, Senator Alan, undated, 1983-1987 (Box 100, Folder 16)
      - Crisas, Andy, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 17)
      - Crown, Ida, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - Ida Crown Jewish Academy of Chicago, undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Cultural Survival, 1982-1983 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - Cushman, Aaron D. (see OS6F Folder 1), 1983 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Cytrynbaum, Stanley, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Dance, undated, 1982, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - Davidson, Alice, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - Davidson, Sandy, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - DeGraff, Mel, undated, 1984-1986 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - DeConcini, Senator, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 10)
      - Defence for Children International, undated, 1987-1989 (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - Defense of AAEJ Materials 1988, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 101, Folder 12)
      - Detroit Group, 1983-1986 (Box 101, Folder 13)
      - Dewoskin, Bill, undated, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 14)
      - Diamond, Jamie, undated, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 15)
      - Diamond, Terry and Marilyn, undated, 1983-1984, 1987-1989 (Box 101, Folder 16)
      - Diaspora Museum (see OS1F Folder 2), undated, 1985-1987 (Box 101, Folder 17)
      - Direct Mail, undated, 1986-1987 (Box 101, Folder 18)
      - Directories, undated (Box 101, Folder 19)
      - Direct Relief International, undated, 1982-1983 (Box 101, Folder 20)
      - Djibouti, 1986-1988 (Box 101, Folder 21)
      - Doctors Project Gondar, undated, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 22)
      - Doidge, Mark, undated, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 23)
      - Donations, undated (Box 101, Folder 24)
      - Drought, 1983-1984 (Box 101, Folder 25)
      - Dublin, Dr. Robert, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 26)
      - Duke, Albert, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 27)
      - Duro-Test, undated, 1974, 1980, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 28)
      - Eaton, Joseph, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Edelstein, Jack, 1985-1986 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Egandorf, Alfred, 1986-1987 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Eitches, 1985-1986 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - EJ Organizations - Other, undated, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Elias, Rabbi Robert - Program: Israel, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - Encyclopedia of Jewish Institutions, undated, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - Encyclopedia Judaica, undated (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - Encyclopedia Judaica - Decennial Book 1973-1982 "The Jews of Ethiopia", circa 1983 (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - England - John Cable, John Peters, undated, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 10)
      - England Group, undated, 1984-1985, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 11)
      - England - Minister of State, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 12)
      - England - Parfitt, Tudor, 1985 (Box 102, Folder 13)
      - Envelopes - Fundraising, undated (Box 102, Folder 14)
      - Eritrea, 1983-1987 (Box 102, Folder 15)
      - Eritrean Community Association of Chicago, undated, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 16)
      - Eritrean Community Center - Chicago, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 17)
      - "ET - EJ" (Educational Tools for Ethiopian Jews) campaign (contains photograph), 1984 (Box 102, Folder 18)
      - Ethiopia - Articles, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 102, Folder 19)
      - Ethiopia - Background, undated, 1984, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 20)
      - Ethiopia - Disease Outbreak Information: November/December 1985 (Box 102, Folder 21)
      - Ethiopia, Inc. - The Universal Sons and Daughters of, undated, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 22)
      - Ethiopia - Political Asylum Backup Information, 1977-1979, 1982-1984 (Box 102, Folder 23)
      - Ethiopia - Political Asylum Backup Information, undated, 1985-1987 (Box 102, Folder 24)
      - Ethiopia - Politics, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 25)
      - Ethiopia - Prisoners, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 26)
      - Ethiopia - Religious Repression, undated, 1982-1983 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Ethiopia, Somalia, Djibouti - Country Profile, 1986-1987 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Ethiopia - Travel, undated, 1985, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Ethiopia - Various, undated (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Ethiopian Aid Organization - Project Mercy, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Ethiopian Airlines (Chicago), 1983 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Ethiopian Artifacts - Sudan, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Ethiopian / Chicago Articles, undated, 1986, 1989-1990 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Ethiopian-Chicago - Ethiopian Jews, undated (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - Ethiopian Committee on Immigration, undated, 1982-1986 (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - Ethiopian Community Associaton of Chicago (see OS1F Folder 2), undated, 1982, 1984-1990 (Box 103, Folder 11-12)
      - Ethiopian Community Development Council, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 13)
      - Ethiopian Community Development Inc. / Washington, D.C., 1984, 1987-1989 (Box 103, Folder 14)
      - Ethiopian Conference - MSU 1983 (Box 103, Folder 15)
      - Ethiopian Embassy, 1985-1986 (Box 103, Folder 16)
      - Ethiopian - Famine Relief Project, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 17)
      - Ethiopian Hunger Watch Committee, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 18)
      - Ethiopian-Israel Addresses (AAEJ Cases), undated (Box 103, Folder 19)
      - Ethiopian Jewish Organization of Canada (EJOC), 1987 (Box 103, Folder 20)
      - Ethiopian Jewish Committee of Northern California, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 21)
      - Ethiopian Jewry Madrichims Choveret, undated (Box 103, Folder 22)
      - Ethiopian Jews - Exodus of a Tribe - Los Angeles Times, July 7, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 23)
      - Ethiopian Jews - Israel, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 24)
      - Ethiopian - Meningitis, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 25)
      - Ethiopian Mission, January 1983 (Box 103, Folder 26)
      - Ethiopian Refugee Bulletin - Baltimore, 1981-1984 (Box 103, Folder 27)
      - Ethiopian Refugee Mutual Association - St. Paul, MN, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 28)
      - Ethiopian Refugees Mutual Aid Association (St. Louis), undated, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 29)
      - Ethiopian Resumes, undated, 1982, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 30)
      - Ethiopian Tee Shirts, undated (Box 103, Folder 31)
      - Ethiopian Village, 1985, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 32)
      - Ethiopians - Non-Jewish Letters, 1985-1986 (Box 103, Folder 33)
      - Events, undated, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 34)
      - Everett, Edith and Henry, undated, 1983-1987 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Ezra, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Facets Multimedia Inc., undated (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Fact Sheets, undated, 1980-1981, 1984-1985 (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Fahn, Roberta Article and Report, October 1986 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - "The Falasha Game", 1982 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - "Falashas: The Forgotten Jews of Ethiopia" by David Kessler, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - "Falasha No More" (see OS6F Folder 1), undated, 1985-1986 (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - Falasha Rally, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Famine (see OS1F Folder 2), undated, 1983, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - Famine - Action 1984-1985, undated, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - Famine - Ethiopia, 1987-1988 (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - Famine, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 13)
      - Fascell, Dante representative, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 14)
      - Federations, undated, 1982-1986 (Box 104, Folder 15)
      - Federation Donors, undated, 1982, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 16)
      - Feinberg, Abraham, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 17)
      - Feinstein, Steve, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 18)
      - Feltman, David, undated, 1983, 1985-1986 (Box 104, Folder 19)
      - Ferber, Irwin, 1984-1985 (Box 104, Folder 20)
      - Film (see OS1F Folder 2), undated, 1981-1984, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Film Advertising (see OS1F Folder 2), undated, 1984-1985 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Film Advertising: "Exile of the Black Jews" (see OS1F Folder 2), undated, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Film - Ann Arbor - March 1984 (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Film: "Behold the Child", undated (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Film Brochure, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Film: Chicago Viewing, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Film - Coordinator Kit, 1983-1984 (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Film - Epilogue, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - Film - Flitterman, Tamara, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - Film - Hemisfilm Best Film Award - January 1984 (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - Film - LA Cineplex - October 1983, 1983-1984 (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - Film - New York Screening, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 13)
      - Film Proposal - Henry Gold, undated, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 14)
      - Film Proposal - Matara Productions, undated, 1983-1986 (Box 105, Folder 15-16)
      - Film Screening Brochure, undated (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Film Screenings, 1983-1984 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Film Transcript, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Film - Videos of It Brochure (A.B. Data), 1984 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Film - Videotapes of, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Filmakers Library, 1983-1984 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Films, undated, 1984-1987 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Nate's Speech - Israel - 1983, undated, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - National Center for Jewish Film, undated, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - National Conferences, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - NCEC, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - NCEC Mailing, August 1986 (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - NCEC Mailing (1974-1987 update), July 1987 (Box 106, Folder 13)
      - NCEC Mailings (drafts), 1986 (Box 106, Folder 14)
      - NCEC Passover Mailing, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 15)
      - NCEC Passover Mailing, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 16)
      - NCEC Prospective Mailing, November 1986 (Box 106, Folder 17)
      - NCEC Prospective Mailing - April 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 106, Folder 18)
      - NCEC Services, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 19)
      - National Council of Jewish Women, 1984, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 20)
      - National Council of Returned Peace Corps Volunteers (see OS1F Folder 3), 1986, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 21)
      - National Jewish Post and Opinion, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 22)
      - NJCRAC - Mati Elias Trip, December 1983, undated, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 106, Folder 23)